- Prove it.
- Knock-knock.
- Who's there?
- lnterrupting physicist.
- lnterrupting phys...
- Muon. Ha, ha.
Anyway, I got a little residual check
from my commercial.
And I thought, "How about I get the guys
a little thank-you to pay them back?"
(Penny:)So, Sheldon... Ta-da.
A vintage, mint-in-box 1975
Mego Star Trek Transporter...
...with real transporter action. Hot darn!
- Where did you get that?
- From Stuart at the comic-book store.
(Leonard:)You went to the comic-book store
by yourseIf?
(Penny:)Yeah. It was fun.
l walked in and two different guys
got asthma attacks.
FeIt pretty good.
(Sheldon:)Well, this calls for an expression
of gratitude.
(Penny:)Ooh, am I about to get
a rare Sheldon Cooper hug?
No, not this time.
Then they wouldn't be special.
Click. Thanks, Penny.
(Penny:)You're welcome.
(Penny:)Don't worry, I didn't forget about you.
Leonard, I got you a label-maker.